|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
Here in Jeonbugwan we record all the stars
There is also one that appeared on your birthday. Do you want to see?
Yes dad
Okay, let's go
Here
My father studied the stars and made notes about them
Because he was a magician who reads the constellations
Madam!
Stay here and don't go out
If you see your father, run
Don't let him catch you
Father...
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, tommo
I'll give you strength
Will you come with me?
On the day my father was killed by the four Daeho families,
I followed Jin Moo
I was raised completely cut off from the world.
in the deep and dangerous valleys of Danhyanggok
I don’t know, I survived because I’m strong,
or strong because she survived
When my past and my father were forgotten
I'm finally back as Naxu
But Naxu is dead
I came back here as Moo Deok
with a helpless owner,
who at the same time is my disinterested student
How much longer do we have to go?
This bracelet weighs a ton
Teacher, your student is tired
I've had enough. I can't go anymore
I carry all the things!
I am the master and you are my maid
It's your job
When necessary, I am your teacher,
and the maid, when you please?
Of course
And I didn't know
that there is such a place outside the city
This place is so harsh that you can't even hear an echo here.
Hence the name, Danhyangok
And I hear an echo
It's just a figure of speech!
The name is moronic
I want to eat
I lived over there
You will eat what I bring
and sleep where you fall asleep after a hard day
What is this? Smells like chicken
- Do they sell chickens here?
-Who will sell chickens here?
You feel it too, right?
I'm telling you it's chicken
I'm sure. I love chicken
How did you get up there?
Someone is frying chicken nearby
Come down. Why did you go there?
Do you see? Chicken
I told you it smells like her. How cool it is here
Why is all this here?
Moo Dok!
There's even a bath here
Moo Deok,
there is a mountain of food and even a place to swim
Master, you had a good home
Was it necessary to scare the student like that?
So strange...
And there is a blanket
So softly. Cute and comfortable
It's all not mine
Someone lives here
Moo Deok,
Shall we eat chicken? She's already well prepared
Moo Deok?
Is this a man?
Come on, stand!
Calm down
good boy
Well trained. Do you live here?
This is not a stray dog
Where is your master?
Hey fluffy, bring your master
What a smart dog
Who is this?
These can't be Dan Zhu's people
This one doesn't try to hide or hide
Tea
We are guests, so we can have a cup, right?
Watch what you eat and drink
First we need to check who lives here
Then we'll decide what to do next.
So you really don't know?
What?
There is a dog, flowers everywhere,
chicken and tea is boiling
And I almost made a mistake
What are you talking about?
I decided that you were trying to kidnap me and live with me,
hiding behind training
If this dog would wag his tail at you,
I would think that this is all your plan
There's enough room for two or three kids.
Everything was different here when I lived here
The place was lifeless
and perfect for training, that's why I brought you here
So, training?
Was this just on your mind?
Forget! Eat and drink what you want, go ahead
Let them kill you
That's right
I didn't think she would react like that to a simple joke
It's my own fault for following her into this wilderness.
There are no words
Remain a clueless heir
Chan family
I'd rather stay here
than I will live like this
Today is the head of Jinyeowon
convened the magicians of Deho at the Unified Council
All 11 families present except Chang Gan
Is my fight with Chan Wook such a big deal?
This is a duel between magicians and the royal family
The last one was hundreds of years ago
I'm just trying to punish Chan Wook
for looking down on me
These are not personal scores
His Majesty gave the order and the magicians gathered
If they agree, an official match will take place
A gap has appeared that has destroyed stability and peace,
existed between the palace and the magicians
Do you really agree with the decision to deprive Wook of his rights to become the next Gwangju?
Yes, it's true
The duel is only
will resolve the misunderstanding between the Crown Prince and Uk
And regarding Gwangju
I already have a candidate that I want to nominate
Escape does not equal defeat
I heard he ran away before the fight was even announced.
What a shame
He must fight honestly and die with dignity, like a magician
Chan Wook didn't have the guts to do this
Everyone here was his teacher
- Yes
- He was never distinguished by talent
I am against magicians being disgraced like that
What if we deprive Chan Wook of his status as a magician?
If we unanimously deprive him of this status,
will have to take all his energy, he will lose his strength
Are you proposing to ruin the young man's whole life?
But this will help sort out the fight
Anyway, the gate of his energy was closed because of his father.
- He's right
- There is a meaning
Each of you
was Uka's teacher
How can you talk so carelessly
about ruining the life of someone who was once your student?
Sosnovy Bor accepted the terms of the palace
We will accept the shame that may or may not fall
Then let this be an official duel between Sosnovy Bor and the palace
Yes
I heard Uk mastered Ryusu in a very short time
Was he taught by someone from the forest?
It doesn't matter where he goes, to whom,
there is no teacher for him
The water is nice and clean. Skin has become softer
Maybe it's mineral
Moo Deok, the owner of the house is a very neat person
I don't think he'll come back...
That's it
Sound asleep
Of course you're tired
We could have walked calmly, but you were in a hurry
You are now Moo Deok, not Nak Soo. You don't have enough strength
How...
Heavy
Stupid
If it was that hard, you should have asked for help.
So soft
I'm the boss
and she is a maid. That's right
I should sleep here
Somehow I feel uncomfortable
Okay
teacher,
good night to you
How inconvenient
You say there's a nomad inside?
How interesting
Without your help, I wouldn't have recognized her
because there is no malice in her soul
It's better for you to die at my hands than to become wild and petrified
There's an amazing soul in this body
She should have gone wild by now, considering how weak this body is
Why is she still okay?
I don't feel any energy. Where did she all disappear to?
Who are you?
Get away from Moo Deok
This sword was given by the King of Gwangju, Jeonbugwan.
Who are you?
What are you doing next to a girl like that?
Moo Deok, run!
Finally woke up
Who is this?
Yesterday's man
Yesterday's man?
Yes. Don't remember?
Moo Deok, run!
I'm sorry about yesterday
I saw someone in the house
and you suddenly pulled out a sword, I had no choice
Yes, I was scared myself
I still have trouble controlling the energy in my hand
I didn't mean to hurt you
You two...
fought?
Do you really remember nothing?
No
You stood right there and looked at us
Me?
What?
I think you're sleepwalking
I will give you medicinal herbs for this. Brew tea and drink
Are you a doctor?
No, but he's here to collect some herbs,
which can only be found here
Call me Master Li
There's enough room for us here
feel at home
Okay, Sapsari
You really don't remember?
Did I really sleepwalk?
I was lying on the floor...
This nomad is special
A special soul in such a weak body
Let's get to know her better
Don't lie
Seriously! I shifted you so that you can sleep more comfortably
What kind of relationship are you in?
Married?
- No
I didn't sleep on the bed. I was lying on the floor
Why should I lie? I really...
- You always lie
- Probably married
- Not at all
Well, did you win?
No, I lost. But...
He is very strong
- He...
- You're lucky. I knew it
What?
They even gathered a council. Things are getting complicated
Do you think Wook and Moo Deok are okay?
They went to Sari, Mu Dok's home village
She's happy, I guess
Why should she be happy?
She had to leave you
- And?
- Well, you're an idiot
Moo Deok is in love with you
She said so
to help Uku
Yes, yes, of course
I heard Mr. Chan ran away
He didn't run away, he just hid for now
What's the difference?
So he went to Danhyangok with Moo Deok?
- Danhyangok?
- Yes
She recently set off fireworks there on the orders of Mr.
I remember seeing them
I found out that they went there because it was close
- Am I right?
- No
Moo Dok with Wook in Sari Village
Oh, I see. Sari
Don't tell anyone that Uk is there
Okay, I won't tell
Bon appetit
Mu Deok to Danhyangok?
The place is very dangerous
Is that where you kept your pet bird?
You twisted your ankle there and scared everyone
Yes, in Danhyangok
I forgot everything about this place
The fire is weak
His body is full of energy considering his strength
He is the master of Chipsu
Chips? So he's as strong as me
It's clear why it was so hard to beat him
It uses energy to keep the fire going
He moved on
than Ryusu
Ryusu?
He's stronger than me. I could have gotten hurt a lot
The rain wet my clothes
This is Chisu
He dried his clothes so easily
This is the highest degree of Chisu
Highest degree?
I could have died
Now it's dry
Don't drink this tea
Have you drunk everything?
Yes
Are you okay? Does anything hurt?
Is this a poisonous infusion?
No, of course
Prutnyak decoction
Prutnyak?
Prutnyak decoction?
You talked about herbs that only grow in Danhyangok
Were you talking about twigs?
Do you know about him?
I heard that magicians drank this tea...
He lowered libido and they trained calmly
Libido? What is this?
Carnal desire, one of the five human needs
Carnal...
Prutnyak lowers...
the energy that causes this desire
I heard about a magician who reached a high level of witchcraft
He succeeded because he lowered his libido and improved
They say he wears only hemp clothes,
That's why Master Li was nicknamed "Master Hemp Li"
Are you smart for a simple maid?
It is an honor for me to meet a magician of such a level
Greetings, Master HempLi
owner,
Why are you sitting? Say hello
So... my libido is already quite the same?..
No...
Not this...
This can't happen. Help me
One kettle is not enough for this
Are you sure? Tell me the truth!
This is true. If you're so worried,
I'll brew another tea that will put everything back in place
Thank you
Master Li
Can you help my master?
His energy has accumulated in his right hand and he cannot control it
Can you teach him how to cope?
It won't be difficult to teach him
But! To learn from me you have to follow everything I say.
Are you ready for this?
He's ready for anything
Really?
What exactly do I need to do?
Like me
drink a decoction of twig
Ready to downgrade
libido?
Have you emptied the entire kettle?
Yes
Can you do it?
So what if he's a famous magician?
He doesn't have a student and he's hanging around for no apparent reason.
With his help everything will go faster
You will be able to control the energy in your right hand
Hey, he wants me to drink this chastity tea. What's the point?
I'm already worried about how much I drank yesterday
I doubt that this tea will be enough,
to get it all back
This makes sense
Not such a bad idea
Now you don't need increased libido
So, for some time I won’t have any desires?
Moo Deok, look me in the eyes and tell me
Yes! And what?
Think for yourself. This is a rare opportunity
Not every fool is lucky enough to meet someone like him
A little abstinence
and get rid of it
This is not a walk in the garden, I don’t need it here!
Celibacy is an insignificant sacrifice for a high-level magician
Just listen!
You don’t care even if I ruin everything for myself there forever!
Stop making mountains out of molehills!
It's important to me, whether I use it or not!
Hey...
Hey Moo Deok, are you okay?
What just happened?
Ryusu
The energy leaked out of you
A little energy and such a burst of strength
If you took off the bracelet and used all your strength,
I would have died on the spot
Hey, you're bleeding...
Teacher, are you completely crazy?
- Do you like the idea that you could die?
- Yes
It means you're getting stronger
It may seem insignificant now,
but soon you will have more energy
and your strength will become as impressive as Gyeongjeongdaeho Lake
Then I too can regain my strength
Wipe the blood from your forehead before it drenches Gyeongjeongdaeho
Does it hurt?
Not at all
Stop being brave
First year of King Go San's reign
April 1st
Go San, Year One, April 1st
The King's Star lit up in the night sky on the boy's birthday
No one should know about this
But Jeongbugwan probably made a note
I took out a real sign from there
In Jeonbugwan
fake without star
Don't let anyone know the secret of his birth
Have you seen a strange constellation?
It's Wook's birthday and Lady Do Hwa's death.
I heard about the advice
All the venerable magicians have gathered because of me
Deputy of Gwangju,
why don't you start your genealogy?
By a single vote,
you too may be recognized as a venerable magician
I am from the Jin family. Jinyeowon is the place where I was born
What brought you to Jeonbugwan?
The nomad who was found in Sosnovy Bor
was an astrologer from Jeonbugwan
The magicians of Jeongjingak began an investigation,
provide assistance
What investigation?
And if I tell you, will you hide all the evidence?
I have nothing to hide
They can come anytime
They're already here
This magician should have
constantly maintain the right amount of energy here
He was responsible for this place
What? Body in Jeonbugwan?
Eunuch Kim extracted all his energy, body in secret room
There was nothing special about his work
Perhaps a remark for secretly looking at constellation signs
Uncle
Many scientists have disappeared here
Where could they have disappeared to?
Thanks for your help
Nothing special
I have one more request
Maybe it's too much
but I would like to take a look at Jeonbugwan's secret room
You can look around
Take the body out through the underground passage
If they hide something they will try to get rid of it
Keep an eye on his people
Faster
We saw this cart leave Jeonbugwan
Are you magicians?
Show your faces
We want to see what's inside
Let's get him
The man ran away
Have you lost it?
This was inside
Spirit Amulet
Are they from Sosnovy Bor?
There was a spirit amulet in the cart
There shouldn't be any questions
Nak Su helped us even after death
Sorry for the trouble, Deputy Gwangju
You attacked a man in the middle of the street?
I transferred your worthless soul to a worthy body,
but you had no right to show off
Sorry
Deliver this chest
Make sure it gets into the right hands
I'll take care of it right away
It's time to get rid of him
Find me another eunuch
Or I'll move your soul into his body
In the body of a eunuch?
What? Don't like it?
I'll follow your order
Do you still carry the Reflector with you?
Yes
I was thinking about refraining from transmigrating souls because of Sosnovy Bor
But apparently this is the only way to serve His Majesty
The Sosnovy Bor amulet was found in a strange cart,
who left Jeonbugwan
Now we have no right to look for anything there
Find out whose amulet it is
Remember, Uk lost his
And judging by this burnt mark, this is his amulet
Amulet of Uka?
Just think, he escaped, but problems still fall on us
Find Uka
Find out how and where he lost it
- Yes
This is from Jin Moo, Jeonbugwan's deputy
What does he always send you?
These are medicinal herbs for my health
You can't tell by him, but he's very caring.
Moo Deok
Master Li and I will go collect herbs
What about training?
I have to pay for maintenance. See you later
- Let's go
- Yes
Is it really that beautiful there?
- Simply amazing
- I wish I could see you soon
Master Li, you are so clever
I buy everything and put it away. Hold it
- So?
- Yes
Great
Today we'll go to a place full of tangerines*
*Chinese perch
Mandarin ducks? Let's take what we need and prepare fish stew
Can you do it?
No, but you will teach me
What's wrong with you...
Oversalted
Moo Deok, try it
Master, are you here to deal with nonsense?
What are you doing?
There's a lot to learn from Master Li
Who is asking you to learn this?
If you learn from him, learn correctly!
Moo Deok, I think I'm perfect for this kind of life.
Thank you for bringing me
to such a wonderful place
You're not worried
because of the fight with the prince?
If you're so worried, figure it out yourself
I definitely oversalted it
Hey!
Moo Deok, put down the knife
Don't you dare throw it at me!
I said I'll kill you if you're useless
You can't kill me
I mastered Chipsu, and you are just Moo Dok
You are not Nak Soo anymore
Hey, he said it!
You and I don't need peace and tranquility
I'll destroy your world
What's wrong with you?
Why are you stopping me from living peacefully?
Are you satisfied with this life?
Yes!
Absolutely. If you don't like it, leave
I like living here
and you can leave if you are so against it
Scumbag
You know that we are connected by fate
And you want me to finish everything
Coward
I found a way for Uka
avoid the duel and become Jeonbugwan's gwangju
Which one? We are ready for anything
Let him marry my daughter Cho Young
Our family has an amulet that will allow
refuse the king's orders
We might even overthrow the king
if all Daeho mages vote for this
This amulet was entrusted to us by the United Council
to prevent the escape of evil spirits that are sealed in Jinyeowon
You propose to cancel the king's order to deprive Uka of his rights
become the next Gwangju?
Yes, but only if he marries my daughter
and join the Jin family
But Mrs. Jin and Mr. Wook once
The engagement has already been broken. Is this not a problem?
It wasn't because my feelings for him had passed
I still want to marry Uka
I didn't think he'd get married early
And I'm not sure he's ready to get married
You're doing good for a rich man's son
Once I get excited about something, I learn quickly
Now I like you even more
Reconsider your desire to become my student
Master, haven’t you had a single student?
There was one
but he gave up celibacy and got married
He now works in a hospital
You can change your mind and refuse at any time
Think about it
I didn't come here for training.
Do you really want to spend this power?
for fishing and collecting herbs?
- I still don’t control her
- Yes?
This hand will become a burden if you leave it like this
Do you want me to take all the energy?
Then you can live a normal life
I'm going to town. Will you come with me?
No, not today. I have to cook Moo Deok to eat
She's not here. She recently went down the mountain
What?
Chan Wook is just a genius
He has already mastered Ryusu
and is training hard for the fight
Let such a rumor spread throughout the city
Seriously?
If he doesn't show up, he'll lose face completely.
So at least he will feel humiliated
Give me some chicken
Leave today. Here are the people of Jeonbugwan
Someone important came today
It's better not to cross paths with him.
especially after the story with the amulet
Come on, stand!
Are you Chan Wook's maid?
Yes. And what?
Nak Soo would never transfer her soul into such a body.
Hey you
Do you remember we met at the inn by the pier?
I don't even know
He suspects me
I want to ask you a couple of questions. Come with us to Jeonbugwan
Let's go
- Let me go
- Stand still
- Why do you...
- Well, stand
She doesn't have a blue mark
She's right isn't Nak Soo?
I don't know where the owner is
Your Highness
Your Highness, it's me
It's me, Won Moo Deok
You're Won Moo Deok
Yes, it's me. You gave me this name
I am Won Moo Deok
Your Highness, please help me
With what?
Your Highness, you are not just smart, but also very strong
And my master, on the contrary, is stupid and pathetic
Because of him my life is in danger
Please help me
Thank you very much, Your Highness
What is your stupid and pathetic owner doing?
He just cries every day
He's so afraid of you that he's shaking with fear.
and cries secretly
I see that you speak badly of him to please me
I can say worse things if it makes you happy
Won Moo Deok, you must think I'm pathetic
You didn't give me this name for nothing.
You can tell me everything you wanted, but couldn't,
because they were afraid to seem pathetic
Do you want to be a verbal cesspool?
This is too high a title for me
But it would be an honor for me
I don't need you to relieve stress
Your Highness, you have already done enough,
but couldn't you order those people not to take me?
A warning will suffice
Take this
This is my sachet
Sachet - paper or fabric pad (bag) with loose fragrant filling
Show it if your pathetic boss gets you into trouble again.
Thank you very much
It smells like cinnamon
Why do you have such a face?
What? Don't you like it?
No, I really like it
- If you don’t like it, return it
- No
I've already stained it with myself
I thank you for this wonderful smelling gift.
Let me pour you a drink that smells just as good
This is a wine with cinnamon and ginger.
There's a lot of cinnamon in there
You probably don't like it. Return the sachet
No
Like
- Is it delicious?
- Very
Have another drink
Moo Deok probably went to Jwisungra. She has nowhere else to go
Did she get angry and leave?
What kind of maid is this?
She's not just a maid
If she's not just a servant, then who?
Moo Deok is like an egg
She needs to be protected
- Let's go see
- What's there?
They found the corpse of a nomad
- The corpse of a nomad?
- Where?
- Let me take a look
- What happened?
- Holy Heavens
- Horror
Nightmare
This is not a nomad
But he died because of him
Do you know about nomads?
When nomads lose their minds, they absorb people's energy
That is why soul alchemy was banned,
and the nomads began to be caught and killed
Are all the nomads losing their minds?
Only those who don't own Hwangsu
Can a person reach such a level?
Of course
Do you want to become my student and reach this level?
You are not only smart and well built,
you have everything you need for this
Thanks for the compliment, but I don't want to take a vow of celibacy
If you become my student,
I will help you take off this bracelet
"Teacher"
Repeat
Please stop trying to persuade me
We are from Jeonbugwan, make way
I need to go. I can't get in their sight
Look there
- Is this a rainbow?
- Where?
It's a rainbow
- It's really a rainbow
- Beauty
- Take a look
- How long has she been gone?
- Beauty
- Take a look
- It really is a rainbow
-Where did the cart go?
She was here a minute ago
-Where did she go?
-Where is the cart?
It's amazing to hear your echo in Danhyangok
Excellent
What? Is Moo Deok drunk?
You say she was drinking here?
Today they almost took her to Jeonbugwan
But fortunately, the Crown Prince saved her
- Crown Prince?
- Yes
She was good at making him laugh
She found an approach to him
She drank all the glasses he offered her
Where is she?
Drunk as hell
Moo Deok, are you okay?
My student, you came for me
Yes, I came for you, teacher
I have no control over my body
I can't even hold my head straight
This never happened before, no matter how much I drank.
You are no longer a skilled warrior,
just Moo Deok
I can't even drink
I want to leave everything and lead a quiet life
But something bothers me
Thought I fell from a great height
But I guess it wasn't that high
Looks like I broke my leg
Help me
I saw you use it to call your bird
I want to try too
Can I take it?
I've come to give it back to you
Moo Deok
I saw Moo Deok
She's really here
Where is Uk?
I told you not to run
What is it?
Why are you here?
We didn't find you in the village of Sari,
that's why we came here to look for you
Joo Wol was right, you are really here
How are you doing, Moo Deok?
Okay
Moo Deok, you're probably glad to see us
She's drunk
Did she drink?
- Yes
- Saw
Help her up
Pick her up
Mu Deok used to come to Danhyangok to collect medicinal herbs
Master Li lives here, he allowed us to stay here
I can't believe Moo Deok got drunk alone
She's doing well
I didn't know there was such a place in Danhyangok
Did you know about Danhyangok?
He used to come here often
He got it for constantly running away
Yul?
He was crazy about birds
Why did you come here alone?
You even hurt your leg here
Because I wanted to see them
The broken leg didn't bother me
And I wasn't afraid that they would scold me
I loved them very much
He really likes birds
By the way, what kind of tea is this?
- The smell is very pleasant
- What did you drink?
Yes, but what? Is he useful?
Of course
It is made from medicinal herbs,
which grow only in Danhyangok
Really?
- Yulia, you try too...
- Don't drink...
Okay, help yourself
- The smell is really pleasant
- Tell me?
This is chastity tea
What? Chastity?
You won't be able to...
- Is this buttercup tea?
- I don’t know exactly
Well...
There are a lot of different herbs you can drink
Delicious
To your health
A bunch of suspicious men and my amulet?
Yes
Have you really lost your amulet?
Did someone steal it from you or did you lend it to someone?
No, I lost it
Do you remember where and when this happened?
No
We found him while investigating the nomad case.
This is very important and dangerous
Jin Jo Young and Chan Wook's wedding?
Great idea
But those who marry must love each other
He can't marry someone he doesn't love just to solve the problem.
Who would talk about love! All my life I am like a lonely tree in a field. Both!
Wedding is no joke
I've felt love too
One day
I turned away from the master because of love
And it was all in vain
Let's hurry up
getting them married
An unknown person has destroyed our barrier and entered
Ho Yeom, come out and say hello
Who dares call me by name?
Yeom
How are you doing?
Teacher...
teacher
Teacher!
Teacher...
My teacher
Put down your swords! Now!
Moo Deok
Thought you were sleeping. Searched everywhere
Are you still drunk?
Drunk thought I could climb on it
But it's high here. I think I'm coming to my senses
Is that the tree with the nest on top?
Yes
I want to climb this tree again
Did you really climb all the way to the top?
I was Nak Soo then
The moon from there is simply incredible
But I won't see her again
I ran into Dan Zhu's man today
It seems he suspected me
Did you give them my spirit amulet?
I tried to get back with his help
But he killed the one he mistook for me
If they catch me
don't you dare save me
Of course. I'm too weak anyway
Your student can't do anything for you
I didn't expect anything
Moo Deok,
I can't do much, but I can climb a tree
There are no branches above to stand on
We need to use energy to create a foothold.
To do this you need to master Chisa
You care about this like you care about the moon
I didn't want to do anything
but I want to climb this tree
You said you wanted to look at the moon from there
I'm the only one who can help with this
so I'll try
Do you want to go up?
We need to master Chisa, I told you
Do you want it or not?
Then help me
go up there
Okay
I'll take you to the top of this tree
/////////////////////////////////////
Thanks for watching with us!
Space for your advertising!
Alchemy
Shower
How's Uka doing?
Do you know who my real father is?
Nobody expects you to fight him
The next step could bring him closer to death
Does your master know about this?
Did you meet Nak Soo as a child?
I don't know her name or age
Just the place where we looked at the birds
I don't know where she lived
This is where the Jin family lives
Lady Jin's daughter is getting married
What should I do, teacher? Marry?
It's not my plan to be your maid forever